<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <BattleRam.label>Battle ram</BattleRam.label>
  <BattleRam.description>A hypertrophied version of a common rhinoceros beetle, which is difficult to recognize under the layers of pulsating tissue and armor plates. It is extremely resistant to wounds, but its vitality is not infinite. Presumably the first copy was obtained as a result of mutagenic overdoses and injections of Likombinat, and later multiply multiplied, however, not all copies were viable. He is extremely aggressive and rushes to anyone who gets in the way.</BattleRam.description>
  <BattleRam.tools.0.label>head claw</BattleRam.tools.0.label>

  <Goliath.label>哥利亚</Goliath.label>
  <Goliath.description>至今为止发现的最危险的生物之一。\n反应快如闪电，导致近战时难沾其身。不过，薄弱的甲壳能轻易被枪械破开。\n此类生物行走迅速，视力极佳，能几个月不眠不休，但此后可能会突然进入假死状态，可惜的是，死了无数个斥候也未能发现这点。</Goliath.description>
  <Goliath.tools.0.label>左爪</Goliath.tools.0.label>
  <Goliath.tools.1.label>右爪</Goliath.tools.1.label>

  <Bombardier.label>Bombardier</Bombardier.label>
  <Bombardier.description>Outwardly resembles its natural counterpart, but has a huge size.
However, thanks to the reinforced sub-armored chitin plates, the creature is almost not can move efficiently. Early objects had the ability to attack from far away,
which, however, is not seen in modern ones. It is dangerous in close combat.</Bombardier.description>
  <Bombardier.tools.0.label>claw</Bombardier.tools.0.label>

  <Termitnator.label>Termitnator</Termitnator.label>
  <Termitnator.description>Not a large but aggressive insect that leaves deep cuts
and chemical burns when hit by the victim. Attacks melee but no different
speed and reaction from ordinary arthropods. Covered with titanium plates,
which makes it pretty durable. The creature is capable of slow regeneration of its
organism, concentrating.</Termitnator.description>
  <Termitnator.tools.0.label>left claw</Termitnator.tools.0.label>
  <Termitnator.tools.1.label>right claw</Termitnator.tools.1.label>

</LanguageData>